## **Ricky Segura**

I am a former U.S. Army intelligence analyst with a top secret SCI clearance and 3 years of proven experience in information gathering and data analysis. I have IT and finance related work experience as an order processor in Los Angeles for a global textile manufacturing company.

Los Angeles, CA
(818) 299-3298
devrickysegura@gmail.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Neospaces**, Los Angeles — Web Developer

AUGUST 2021 - PRESENT

I have experience with both front and back-end web development, creating projects with modern, responsive designs, server-side programming, API development and integration, database management, website traffic analysis, and SEO, just to name a few things.

### **A1 American**, Pacoima — Order Processor

APRIL 2022 - PRESENT

Processed wire transactions, online credit card payments, and check deposits. Communicated with shipping/warehouse departments about order readiness. Directly reported daily deposits for Los Angeles company HQ to CFO.

### **KPB Taco Bell**, Colorado Springs — Cashier

IANUARY 2022 - APRIL 2022

Provided an exemplary customer experience for each individual customer. Prepared restaurant for opening at the beginning of the day. Worked at the 2nd highest earning Taco Bell in Colorado Springs, CO.

### **US Army**, Colorado Springs — Security Manager

JULY 2018 - DECEMBER 2021

MOS: 35F All-Source Intelligence Analyst - Conducted physical security reviews and audits. Awarded 2 Certificates of Achievement for outstanding performance. File management and security on Windows OS.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **W3Schools**, Colorado Springs — Front End Developer Certificate

AUGUST 2021

Ability to design and create full-stack websites from the ground up. I can implement code changes, manage API integration, understand data analytics, and register domains, just to name a few things.

#### **Portfolio & Relevant Links**

GitHub:

https://github.com/rickysegura

Portfolio:

https://rickysegura.w3spaces.com/

#### **SKILLS**

Web design

Adobe Photoshop

HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Node.js

Problem solving

Teamwork

WordPress

Communication

Time management

Microsoft Office Suite

Customer service

#### **AWARDS**

2x Certificate of Achievement Awarded by US Army for outstanding performance

### **W3Schools**, Colorado Springs — CSS Developer Certificate

AUGUST 2021

Ability to design and create websites using CSS to stylize and customize features by manipulating HTML elements.

## W3Schools, Colorado Springs - HTML Developer Certificate

AUGUST 2021

Ability to construct modern websites with HTML using industry standards and efficient, clean code.

## **W3Schools**, Colorado Springs — *JavaScript Developer Certificate*

AUGUST 2021

Ability to design and create websites. Implement code changes, API integration, data analytics, and domain registration.

## **Computer Science Major,** Valley Glen — *Actively pursuing an associates degree*

# **Birmingham Community Charter High School,** Van Nuys — *High School Diploma*

AUGUST 2015 - OCTOBER 2017

I was in the track & field team, as well as the cross country team. I was active in many academic clubs, such as the student council.

#### **LANGUAGES**

English, Spanish (Intermediate)